<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ArunTimeException</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ArunTimeException</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>You</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:31:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>(WIP) Character encodings</title>
      <link>/posts/2020-08-15-encoding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:31:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2020-08-15-encoding/</guid>
      <description>ASCII I started attending an online class called the Bradfield Computer Science Intensive. I can tell you that I am learning a lot of new and exciting stuff. Stuff I should have learned in college, but didn&amp;rsquo;t. I might write a post about that someday. But for now Ill try and get straight to the point.
Computers only speak one language. Its binary. The only 2 alphabets are [0, 1]. You can also think of them as [On, Off], [Up, Down].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:31:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Github: arunsivasankaran
About me I am a web developer. I live and work in LA. I work on the Platform team for a small startup. I am currently a student at Bradfield CS
This blog is mostly about&amp;hellip;  Stuff I learn at bradfield. My opinions on backend web development.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Algorithms - Graphs</title>
      <link>/posts/2020-05-01-algorithms-graphs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2020-05-01-algorithms-graphs/</guid>
      <description>Undirected Graphs Some problems  Path Shortest path Cycle Ehler tour: A cycle that uses each edge excatly once. Hamilton tour: A cycle that uses each vertex exactly once  classical NP-complete problem.   Connectivity MST: Biconnectivity: A vertex whose removal disconnects the graph Planarity Graph isomorphism: Are two graphs identical?  No one knows so far. A lonstanding open problem    Representations Real-world graphs tend to be sparse (huge number of vertices, small average vertex degree).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>